{
  "heading": "Probability",
  "topics": [
    {
      "heading": "Probability",
      "questions":  [
  {
    "questionNo": 1,
    "question": "A bag contains 5 red and 5 green marbles. What is the probability of picking a red marble?",
    "options": [
      { "text": "50%" },
      { "text": "25%" },
      { "text": "100%" },
      { "text": "20%" }
    ],
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 2,
    "question": "What is the probability of drawing a red card from a standard 52-card deck?",
    "options": [
      { "text": "25%" },
      { "text": "50%" },
      { "text": "100%" },
      { "text": "20%" }
    ],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 3,
    "question": "What does a probability of 0 mean?",
    "options": [
      { "text": "The event will always happen" },
      { "text": "The event is unlikely" },
      { "text": "The event is impossible" },
      { "text": "The event might happen" }
    ],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 4,
    "question": "What is the probability of not drawing a heart from a standard deck?",
    "options": [
      { "text": "25%" },
      { "text": "75%" },
      { "text": "100%" },
      { "text": "20%" }
    ],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 5,
    "question": "A spinner is divided into 8 equal sections. If 2 sections are yellow, what is the probability of landing on yellow?",
    "options": [
      { "text": "0.25" },
      { "text": "25%" },
      { "text": "2/8" },
      { "text": "All of the above" }
    ],
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 6,
    "question": "What is the probability of selecting a Queen from a standard deck of cards?",
    "options": [
      { "text": "4%" },
      { "text": "5%" },
      { "text": "About 7.7%" },
      { "text": "9%" }
    ],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 7,
    "question": "A coin is tossed. What is the probability of getting a head or a tail?",
    "options": [
      { "text": "0" },
      { "text": "0.5" },
      { "text": "1" },
      { "text": "2" }
    ],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 8,
    "question": "A die is rolled. What's the probability of getting an even number less than 4?",
    "options": [
      { "text": "1/6" },
      { "text": "4/6" },
      { "text": "2/6" },
      { "text": "6/6" }
    ],
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 9,
    "question": "A spinner has 5 equal sections: Red, Blue, Green, Yellow, Purple. Whatâ€™s the probability it does not land on Green?",
    "options": [
      { "text": "25%" },
      { "text": "75%" },
      { "text": "20%" },
      { "text": "80%" }
    ],
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 10,
    "question": "A number from 1 to 10 is chosen at random. What is the probability of getting a number that is even and greater than 5?",
    "options": [
      { "text": "25%" },
      { "text": "75%" },
      { "text": "30%" },
      { "text": "80%" }
    ],
    "answer": 2
  }
]
    }
  ]
}